<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resume>

  <institution>
    <name>The Ontario Institute for Studies in Education, OISE</name>
    <time>September 2012 - Present</time>
    <position>Office assistance</position>
    <description>Develop small software using PHP, SQL, JavaScript and HTML to assist daily routine in workplace</description>
    <description>Update the list and calendar and check room booking for workshops and events in OISE</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Altus Strategy Group</name>
    <time>May 2012 - September 2012</time>
    <position>Web developer</position>
    <description>Analyzed, designed and implemented the user managing system (including the database, the interface, the workflow) using HTML, PHP and JavaScript.</description>    
    <description>Worked internationally through email with a team member from China. Our only source of communication is email.</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Private tutor</name>
    <time>May 2012 - September 2012</time>
    <position>Tutor</position>
    <description>Helped a senior with continuing study in Java and C.</description>
    <description>Helped acquaintances in university about first year calculus and first year linear algebra.</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>University college resident community – Hutton house</name>
    <time>September 2011 - May 2012</time>
    <position>Food director</position>
    <description>Collected feedbacks from residents about food services</description>
    <description>Suggested solution to improve quality of resident's meal</description>
    <description>Organized social events</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Resume generator</name>
    <time>2012</time>
    <position>Computer programmer</position>
    <description>Used HTML, JavaScript, XML and CSS file to read job description and create a part of this resume</description>
    <description>Allowed user to change the style, and layout easily</description>
    <description>Ensured high consistency in style and design</description>
  </institution>
  
  <institution>
    <name>“Research in action show case”, University of Toronto</name>
    <time>27th March 2012</time>
    <position>Ambassador</position>
    <description>Greeted guests</description>
    <description>Supported the food service during the event</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>University college resident community’s carnival for St. Patrick’s Day </name>
    <time>2012</time>
    <position>Volunteer</position>
    <description>Worked at the reception table</description>
    <description>Helped the setup and tear down</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>The 11th ACSE Conference for ACSE: Association for computer science educators</name>
    <time>12th November 2011</time>
    <position>Volunteer</position>
    <description>Installed projectors in seminar rooms</description>
    <description>Directed high school teachers to registration table and seminar rooms</description>
    <description>Gave technical supports to presenters during presentations</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Fall Campus Days 2011 for Computer science department</name>
    <time>29th October 2011</time>
    <position>Ambassador </position>
    <description>Explained to visitor what computer science is, and why they should take computer science</description>
    <description>Shared experience as a computer science student with high school students</description>
    <description>Conducted a tour for big group of visitor(at least 30 people) around Bahen center</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>“CS student for a day” program for Computer science department</name>
    <time>11th Oct 2011 and 24th Oct 2011</time>
    <position>Ambassador</position>
    <description>Explained to 12 grade students what computer science is, and why they should take computer science</description>
    <description>Shared experience as a computer science student with high school students</description>
    <description>Conducted a tour for 12 grade students around Bahen center</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>National computer science contest</name>
    <time>2011</time>
    <position>Representative of Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam</position>
    <description>Solved computer science problems using dynamic programing, graph algorithms and Pascal as programing language</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Regional computer science contest for high school student</name>
    <time>2010 and 2011</time>
    <position>First prize winner</position>
    <description>Solved computer science problems using dynamic programing, graph algorithms and Pascal as programing language</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>An Ba Joint Stock Pharmaceutical Company</name>
    <time>June 2010 - September 2010</time>
    <position>Computer programmer</position>
    <description>Created a random number generator using Window form in C# and Visual studio 2008 to assist company’s promotion program</description>
    <description>Analyzed, designed and implemented a sufficient data structure and algorithm for the program</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>High school English debate contest</name>
    <time>2010</time>
    <position>Team leader</position>
    <description>Give speeches and presentations on many topics</description>
    <description>Got into the semi-final</description>
    <description>Had to write a creative essay about “The best invention of human” to be qualified for the contest</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Regional science fair for creative idea</name>
    <time>2010</time>
    <position>Leader of second prize winning team</position>
    <description>Constructed model demonstrating how to save a significant amount energy from high-rise’s sewage systems </description>
    <description>Suggested installing a micro power generator at the end point of high-rise’s sewage systems to recapture the energy used to bring water up</description>
    <description>Gave speeches and presentations to defense the project</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Regional computer science contest</name>
    <time>2009</time>
    <position>Member of second prize winning team</position>
    <description>Used Pascal to create simple AI to optimized economic profit in a competitive environment</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Governmental exchange student program in Japan for 1 week</name>
    <time>2008</time>
    <position>Exchange student</position>
    <description>Enhanced mutual understanding between two countries (enjoyed recreational activities with Japanese’s students, stayed with a family for a few days, etc.)</description>
    <description>Learned about different aspect of Japanese culture (food, origami, religion, etc.)</description>
    <description>Met official Japan ambassador in Hanoi, capital of Vietnam</description>
    <description>Met Osaka’s Major and government representatives in Osaka’s City Hall, Japan</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>Australian National Chemistry Quiz</name>
    <time>2007 – 2010</time>
    <position>Participant</position>
    <description>Got Certificates of Distinction  annually</description>
    <description>It is based on critical thinking as well as creative problem solving</description>
  </institution>

  <institution>
    <name>National software contest for high school student</name>
    <time>2010</time>
    <position>Accolade prize winner</position>
    <description>Used C# to build program to support users select wanted files fast</description>
    <description>Gave varied presentations</description>
    <description>Wrote program manuals for users</description>
    <description>Created trailer for the software</description>
  </institution>

</resume>
<!--
<institution>
  <name></name>
  <time></time>
  <position></position>
  <description></description>
</institution>-->


